newrichreport.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
New Rich Report believes that your privacy is very important and we intend to make your experience with us on the Internet to be reliable, safe and secure and we want you to have complete confidence in using our website and services.

Personal Information  
New Rich Report collects information in several different ways from visitors and members who access the various parts of our services and the network of websites accessible through our company.

Members and visitors may be asked to provide personal information when they register for our products or services, including name, address, phone number, billing information (such as credit card information), and the type of personal computer being used to access the services we provide. The personal information collected from visitors and members during their visits to our websites are used to manage the visitor's requests for information and the member's accounts. This information may be shared with third parties, as stated herein, or in special circumstances.

In instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our services, we may provide the partner certain personal information, such as name, address, and username or members who subscribed to the services as a result of the joint promotion of the offering, products, or services.

Also, with purchases or inquiries, we may supply the visitors or members contact information to our business partners, who may contact the visitor or member by telephone, email, or mail, with offers in conjunction with the website visited or offers that we believe would be of interest to our visitors and members, with or without compensation from those companies or partners.

Our company uses "cookies", which is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit a certain website. Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for purposes stated herein as well as for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.

You must be eighteen (18) years or older to access this website. If you are under eighteen years of age, you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. Due to the age restrictions for use of this website, no information obtained by this website, falls within the child online privacy act (copa) and is not monitored as doing so.

Websites and services that we own have measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our networks and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party hackers from illegally obtaining this information.

Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Service, our Policies and Procedures and our other policies and agreements at any time in any manner, by updating this or other postings. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Last updated: September 9, 2009
